[TH] Where are the others?
[TH] Ryuji: They've probably gone back to their previous lives.
[TH] Keith: Fighting's the only thing I'm good at.
[TH] I guess I'll try to find someone who'd hire me in Africa.
[TH] J. J.: I got all the money I need from this war.
[TH] I'm going back to my family in Africa.
[TH] I'm not like you, Keith. I don't need to kill to make a living.
[TH] Keith: Huh. A bit harsh on your old partner, aren't you?
[TH] What the hell. Maybe I'll go visit this family of yours.
[TH] ...It was fun, guys.
[TH] Ryuji: Family...
[TH] Too many things have happened ever since I left mine...
[TH] Too much fighting...
[TH] Too much loss...
[TH] I think... I think I need time to sort everything out...
[TH] Captain... This is where we part ways, I'm afraid.
[TH] ...Goodbye, Captain.
[TH] Nathalie: I'm worried about my father...
[TH] Many will view his actions as acts of treason...
[TH] He may have already been sent to the mainland. I must go find him.
[TH] Goodbye... \NM00...
[TH] Gentz: Unlike the others, I have no other life to return to.
[TH] All I can do is make Huffman a safe place for us to live in...
[TH] \NM00... You and I are much alike.
[TH] Join me. There'd be nothing the two of us can't do.
[TH] \NM00: I can't...
[TH] There's something I want--
[TH] no, something I need to do first...